人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
翻译    苏葵
校对    苏葵
时间轴    壬虚浪影
后期    渔夫
喂
Hello?
他们找到尸体了
They've found a body.
总监    苏葵
我知道
I know.
我就在现场
I'm down there now.
你觉得这有联系吗
Do you think it's linked?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
一会就会知道
I'm about to find out.
比利
Billy?
你还在吗
Are you still there?
谁报的警
Who called it in?
听说是个遛狗的人
Some guy walking his dog, apparently.
可怜的家伙
Poor bastard.
那会毁了你的一整天
That would ruin your day.
好  有事通知我
OK, keep me updated.
乔
Hey, Joe!
我是克里斯申  请留言
This is Christian. Say something.
不
No...
他撒谎了
He's lied...
关于他的家庭  关于碧昂卡
..about his family, about Bianca.
一切都是谎言
Everything's a lie!
达沃  拜托  一切都是谎言
Davor, please... Everything's a lie!
听我说  我现在知道了  一切都是谎言
..listen to me. I know now... Everything's a lie!
...我在哪看到过那辆车了
..where I've seen that car before.
在我们死之前
第四集
-我只是  -亲爱的  你看着很担心  你很担心
- I just... - Honey, you look worried, you are worried.
这很正常  但没关系
I mean, it's natural, but it's fine.
他会回来的
He'll turn up.
好吗
Yeah?
谢谢
Thanks.
回头见
See you soon.
听着  如果他联系你
Listen, if he does get in touch,
-你就发信息给我  或者...  -好
- you-you'll text me or... - Yeah.
我可以让你们俩处理  对吧
So I can leave you two to it, yeah?
你有一条新信息
You have one new message.
汉娜  我不确定你在哪或在干什么
Hannah, I'm not sure where you are or what you're up to,
但你能尽快来老地方见我吗
but will you meet me back at the usual place as soon as possible?
很重要
It's important.
克里斯申
Christian?
克里斯申  什么
Christian, what...
你在干什么  住手
What are you doing? Stop it.
放开我
Get your hands off me.
克里斯申  住手
Christian, stop it!
够了  你听到了吗
Enough! Do you hear me?
比利  怎么回事
Billy, what has happened?
斯特凡·瓦盖奇死了
Stefan Vargic is dead.
你杀了他
You killed him!
不
No!
克里斯申  天呐
Christian... Oh, my God.
-住手  -是你的朋友  米密查家族
- Stop it. - Your friends, the Mimicas,
对  但你差不多也算扣下了扳机
Yeah, but you might as well have pulled the trigger!
住手  克里斯申  克里斯申
Stop it! Christian... Christian!
你觉得会怎么样
What did you expect?
-我不知道  克里斯申  我以为  -什么
- I don't know, Christian. I thought that... - What?
跟警察交好能给他一枚奖牌吗
Give him a gold fucking star for cosying up a police officer?
我觉得你最好离开  比利
I think you'd better go, Billy.
我是想保护你
I was trying to protect you.
克里斯申
Christian...
Christian?
坐起来
Sit up.
喝掉这个
You drink this.
是什么
What is it?
加了白兰地的茶
It's tea with brandy.
你受惊了
You're in shock.
你在场吗
Were you there?
你看到事发经过了吗
Did you see it happen?
谁打死了他
Who shot him?
拜托  克里斯申  这很重要
Please, Christian, it's important.
谁打死了斯特凡
Who shot Stefan?
拜托
Please...
克里斯申
Christian...
谁打死了他
..who shot him?
我快结束了
I'm almost finished.
怎么了
What is it?
大家都在哪
Where is everyone?
谁
Who?
斯特凡  克里斯申
Well, Stefan, Christian.
我联系不到他们俩
I can't get hold of either of them.
你为什么联系克里斯申
Why are you calling Christian?
问他有没有看到斯特凡
To ask if he's seen Stefan.
斯特凡在克罗地亚
Stefan is in Croatia.
从什么时候开始
Since when?
昨晚
Last night.
怎么  都不说再见吗
What, without saying goodbye?
他需要消失
He needed to disappear.
他干了什么
What did he do?
你知道最好别问
You know better than to ask that.
他什么时候会回来
And when will he be back?
他不回来了
He's not coming back.
这不会改变我对你的看法
This doesn't change the way I feel about you.
你知道  对吧
You know that, right?
它改变了我对自己的看法
It changes the way I feel about myself.
-不是他死就是你亡  -妈
- It was him or you. - Mum.
我对他的死不感到惋惜
I-I'm not sorry he's dead.
别说了
Please, stop.
我不在乎别人
I don't care about anyone.
我只在乎让你离开这危险的局面
I just care about getting you out of this mess.
我得回去了
I have to go back.
那不行
Well, that's not gonna happen,
因为我不允许
because I won't allow it.
他们不会让我就这样离开
They won't just let me walk away.
那你就躲起来
Then you'll go into hiding.
下半辈子都躲吗
For the rest of my life?
直到我们抓到他们
Until we nail them.
那是什么时候
And when will that be?
你没有任何线索证明米密查家族和肖恩的死有关
You have nothing to link the Mimicas to Sean's murder.
没有我  你根本没有机会把他们绳之于法
And without me you've got no chance pulling the stroke of bastards.
我不再在乎了
I don't care any more.
跟达沃说  告诉他你受够了想退出
Talk to Davor, tell him that you've had enough and you want out.
他有你用过的枪
He's got the gun that you used.
他知道你不会告密
He knows you'll keep your mouth shut.
否则他会让自己受牵连
He'd have to incriminate himself.
他不会冒这个险
He'd never risk it.
你会告诉蒂娜吗
Will you tell Tina?
不会
Nothing.
她不必知道
She never needs to know.
比利呢
And Billy?
别担心比利
Don't worry about Billy.
他会想明白的  如果他还没发现的话
He'll work it out, if he hasn't already.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
克里斯申确定是他
Christian ID'd him.
他看到了吗
Did he witness it?
我想没有
I don't think so.
-但他可以作证  -不行
- But could he testify? - No.
他还好吗
Is he all right?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
但他现在接受我们得撤出他了吗
But does he accept now that we have to pull him out?
不行
No.
他认为米密查家族是在交易前清理内务
He thinks the Mimicas were tidy in-house before the deal.
他并不知道
He can't be sure of that.
但他是深入虎穴的人
But he's the man on the ground here.
他很坚信有大事要发生
He's adamant something big's about to happen.
而且他很安全
And that he's completely safe.
听着
Look,
如果我们抓到他们现场交易白粉
if we can catch them in the act of smuggling the coke,
再加上克里斯申的录音
along with the audio Christian's recorded
和肖恩电脑里的文件
and the files from Sean's computer,
这就是实打实的铁证
it all adds up to a solid bust.
这证明了肖恩在追查他们
It proves Sean was onto them,
并且对方有杀他的动机
and a motive for his murder.
但如果我们不把斯特凡的事告诉凯恩
But if we don't tell Kane about Stefan
之后他发现我们早就知道  那...
and it comes out later that we knew, then...
你有合理的借口
You have plausible deniability.
这都是国家犯罪调查局的
This is all masterminded by some
流氓探员一手策划的
rogue operative from the NCA.
这差不多也是事实
Which is more or less the bloody truth.
你说过我们有72小时
You said we had 72 hours.
对
Yeah.
而且时间快到了
And they're almost up.
流浪者回来了
The wanderer returns.
你可算回来了
There you are.
你见到斯特凡了吗
Have you seen Stefan?
没有
No.
达沃说他回克罗地亚了
Davor said he's in Croatia.
-克罗地亚  -对  他是这么说的
- Croatia? - Well, that's what he said.
克里斯申  怎么回事
Christian, what's going on?
我得跟他谈谈
I have to go and speak to him.
-达沃  -你来迟了
- Davor? - You're late.
一天可以  不能连着两天
One day's OK, not two in a row.
尤其是现在斯特凡在克罗地亚
Especially with Stefan in Croatia.
-对  我想跟你谈谈这个  -坐下
- Yeah, but that's what I wanted to sp... - Sit.
-达沃  我...  -坐
- Davor, I.. - Sit.
我需要你展示出勇气
I need you to show character.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
因为我们谈过的事
Cos the thing we talked about...
克拉伊纳
Krajina.
从今天开始
..it starts today.
克里斯申
Christian...
过去的已经过去了
..what's done is done.
我是克里斯申  请留言
This is Christian. Say something.
别又玩失踪
Not again.
我想他肯定有理由
I'm sure there's an explanation.
已经快两小时了
It's been almost two hours.
我再给他发信息
I'll try texting him again.
天呐
Oh, God.
你得冷静
You need to calm down.
不能带手机
No phones.
有消息吗
Anything?
信号肯定很弱
The signal must be weak.
有了
There we go.
那是哪里
Well, where's that?
玛丽娜酒店
The Marina Hotel.
先生们  欢迎来到布里斯托
Gentlemen, welcome to Bristol.
上校
Colonel?
-我们说过不能带手机  -放松
- We said no phones. - Relax.
我忘记告诉他们了
I forgot to tell them.
我们都是朋友
We're all friends here.
看着熟悉吗
Look familiar?
那是什么
What's that?
我们喝一杯吧
Let's have a drink, huh?
他戴着监听器
He's carrying a bug.
监听器
A bug?
敬成功行动
To a successful operation.
见鬼
Shit.
告诉我  你的旅途还顺利吗
So, tell me, how was your trip?
不太牢靠
Shaky.
这家伙怎么回事
What's wrong with this guy?
抱歉
Sorry.
也许  他病了
Maybe...he's sick?
让他出去
Get him out of here.
你觉得他需要支援吗
Do you think he needs backup?
不  让他去
No, leave him.
他心中有数
He knows what he's doing.
我不能坐视不管
I can't just sit here.
汉娜  你要去哪
Hannah? Where are you going?
我们会付这些
This is what we'll pay.
老天
Come on...
挺住
Come on.
克里斯申
Christian.
Christian?
你  你受伤了吗
Are you... Are you hurt?
-你能起来吗  -克里斯申
- Can you get up? - Christian?
克里斯申  你得站起来
Christian, you have to get up.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here!
我在这里
I'm in here!
没事的
It's ok.
你在这干什么
What are you doing in there?
我感觉不舒服
Well, I...don't feel very well.
你得回去了
You need to come back now.
好
Ok.
那就72小时内
Within the next 72 hours, then.
嗯  都行  反正东西不会跑
Yeah, whenever. It's not going anywhere.
我们都一样
It was the same for all of us.
第一次杀人  这是
The first time you kill, it's...
这是对勇气的终极考验
It's the ultimate test of character.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
难以置信  你真是让人头疼  知道吗
Unbelievable. You're a fucking headcase, you know that?
-只有在需要这样的时候  -不
- Only when I need to be. - No.
你太鲁莽了  汉娜
You were reckless, Hannah.
你可能毁了一切
You could've jeopardised everything.
但我没有
Well, I didn't,
我也不需要你跟我说教鲁莽的事  比利
and I don't need a lecture from you on being reckless, Billy.
至少他又回来了
At least he's back in the fold.
你好你好  我是斯特凡
Hello, hello. You've reached Stefan.
请在哔声后留言
Leave a message after the beep.
你好你好  我是斯特凡
Hello, hello. You've reached Stefan.
请在哔声后留言
Leave a message after the beep.
警方正在调查一名男性的死因
Police are investigating the death of a man
其尸体昨天早上于布洛克利附近的森林发现
whose body was found in woods near Brockley yesterday morning.
尸体在早上六点过后
The discovery was made shortly after 6 am
被一名遛狗路人发现
by a member of the public walking their dog.
警方称死者大约二十多岁
The dead man, who police say appears to be in his 20s,
尚未确认身份
has not been identified.
小姐贵姓
So, Miss...?
琼斯  索菲·琼斯
Jones. Sophie Jones.
我同事接了你的电话
My colleagues who took your call,
-他们说你担心你的男友  -对
- they said you were worried about your boyfriend. - Yeah.
我们大吵了一架
We had a massive row.
-那是什么时候  -两天前
- When was this? - Three nights ago.
之后我就没收到他的消息了
I haven't heard from him since.
他叫什么
What's his name?
马蒂  马修·安德森
Matty... Matthew Anderson.
你担心他的人身安全吗
Are you concerned for his welfare?
我在广播里听到
I heard a report on the radio
布洛克利附近发现了尸体
about a body found near Brockley.
-你为什么觉得两者会有联系  -不知道
- Why do you think there's any connection? - I don't know.
他以前闯过祸
He's had his fair share of trouble.
他有犯罪记录吗
Does he have a criminal record?
我们认识前他在帮派里
He was in a gang before we met.
而且他经常去那片森林
And he goes walking in those woods all the time.
你能帮我们进行简单的身份识别吗
Will you be willing to carry out a basic ID check?
马修有什么特殊的标记吗
Does Matthew have any distinguishing marks?
比如什么
Like what?
胎记  疤痕  纹身
Birthmarks? Scars? Tattoos?
他有一些纹身  对
He has a few tattoos, yeah.
能描述一下吗
Can you describe any of them?
谢天谢地  不是
Thank God. No.
不  他没有这种纹身
No, he has nothing like that.
-给  -谢谢
- There we are. - Thank you.
紧急情况  你需要什么服务
Emergency. What service do you require?
警察
Police.
他们要什么
So, what are they buying?
我们不知道
We don't know.
We don't know?
商讨这方面事宜时克里斯申不在屋里
Christian wasn't in the room when it was discussed.
苍天啊
For Christ's sake!
听着  这次感觉不同
Look, this one feels different.
这不是一次性交易
It's not a single deal.
我觉得后面有更大的局
I think it's much bigger than that.
而且这两人不是闹着玩的  我能确定
And these two are serious business, I can tell.
他们肯定在我们的侦查范围里
They've got to be on our radar.
全国警察电脑系统吗
On pnc?
可能吗
Are they fuck!
不
No.
我是说我们的系统
I mean our radar.
那你能问问老同事吧
And you can ask someone, I presume.
听着  我们快要收尾了
Listen, we're at the business end now.
达沃在十天前说还剩三周
Davor said three weeks and that was ten days ago.
最坏的情况
At worst,
这能让我们进行大型白粉缉毒行动
this lead could be our ticket to a massive coke bust.
想想把这个结果交给凯恩
Imagine taking that to Kane
并给他深深鞠个躬
with a great big fucking bow on it.
好吧
All right.
继续查
Keep digging.
听着  我需要你们在总部露露脸
Look, I need you to show your faces at HQ.
我已经快没借口了
I'm running out of excuses.
芙兰  你还在跟进肖恩·哈达克的案子吗
Fran, are you still working the Sean Hardacre case?
必须的
For my sins.
你不是说他们用了自制子弹吗
Didn't you say they used home-made bullets?
对
Yeah.
用了奇怪的西洋棋图案
With some weird chequerboard design
塞进了弹药筒的底部
pressed into the base of the cartridge.
对  我想也是
Yeah, I thought so.
为这个干什么
Why do you ask?
在树林发现的尸体
That body they found in the woods,
用的是同样的子弹
shot with exactly the same ammo.
一枪打在胸上
One to the chest
另一枪爆头毙命
and one to the head to finish him off.
-你确定吗  -百分百
- Are you sure? - Oh, 100%.
不是普通布里斯托
Not exactly the ammo of choice
小混混们会选择的弹药  对吧
of your average Bristol low-life, is it?
谢谢
Thanks.
我觉得他们刚认出了他  如果你感兴趣
I think they've just identified him, if you're interested.
我们就不能在酒店酒吧见面吗  哪怕就一次
Couldn't we meet in a nice hotel bar, just for once?
你的规矩  不是我定的
Your rules, not mine.
这鬼地方
Godforsaken shithole.
这最好是好消息
This better be good.
我们的线人听到老家伙被称为上校
Our source heard the older guy referred to as the Colonel.
如果你仔细看
If you look closely,
会发现另一个人耳朵有残疾
you'll see the other guy has a mangled ear.
在刚果被打掉了
It was shot off in the Congo.
那你认识他们咯
You know them, then?
艾蒂安·德克勒克
Etienne Declerck.
左边是文森特·克莱蒙斯
The one on the left is Vincent Clemens.
以前是比利时特种部队
Belgian special forces back in the day.
军火商
Arms dealers.
雇佣兵
Mercenaries.
他们怎么会出现在你的调查里
How have they popped up on your radar?
他们跟我们盯着的毒贩打了交道
They're playing footsie with a drug gang in our patch.
那你就有问题了  朋友
Then you have got a problem, my friend.
为什么
Why do you say that?
如果你找上他们  八成是要挑起战争
Those are the guys you call if you want to start a war.
没事了
It's OK.
怎么了
What's wrong?
斯特凡死了
Stefan's dead.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我看到照片了
I've seen a photo.
你知道吗
Did you know?
-真的  你不知道吗  -不
- Really, you didn't know? - No.
如果他们能杀他  他们也能杀你
If they can shoot him, they can shoot you, too.
-我得叫停这一切  -为什么  碧昂卡
- I've got to put a stop to this. - Why? Bianca...
不  我已经报警了
No, I've already called the police,
告诉他们死者是斯特凡
told them it was Stefan.
我是匿名举报的
I called anonymously.
碧昂卡
Bianca?
碧昂卡  那些桌子不会自己变干净
Bianca, those tables won't lay themselves.
你还好吗
You ok?
-感觉好些了吗  -嗯  好点了  谢谢
- Feeling better? - Yeah, a little. Thanks.
-达沃  -我不想听
- Davor. - I don't want to hear it.
不是同一把枪
It's not the same gun.
但是同一种子弹
It's the same fucking bullets!
见鬼
Fuck!
我就知道我们不该把他埋在那里
I knew we shouldn't have buried him there.
那我们该怎么办
So, what shall we do?
给他们想要的东西
Give them what they're looking for.
你的人确认他们身份了吗
Did... Did your guy ID them?
他们是军火商
They're arms dealers.
有道理  他们需要武器
Well, that makes sense. They'll need fire power.
这些家伙贩卖的不是那种武器
Not the kind of fire power these guys specialise in.
稍等
Excuse me a second.
天呐
Christ!
怎么了
What?
碧昂卡刚给总部的人匿名举报
Bianca's just given someone at HQ an anonymous tip off...
关于斯特凡
..about Stefan.
见鬼  我们知道是谁吗
Shit! Do we know who?
他没说
He doesn't say.
天呐  他们会联系到米密查家族
Oh, God, they'll make the connection to the Mimicas
然后找到克里斯申
and then onto Christian.
蒂娜联系你了吗
Has Tina called you?
没有  但她肯定要疯了
No, but she'll be losing her shit.
我们有人得跟她谈谈
Well, one of us needs to speak to her.
我去吧
I'll do it.
-汉娜  -薇姬
- Hannah. - Hi, Vicky.
我不知道你今天会来
I didn't know you were coming in today.
大家都在哪
Where is everyone?
在大会议室
The big meeting room.
嗯  我最好悄悄溜进去
Right. Better stick my head in.
芙兰  汉娜请了病假
And, Fran, Hannah is off sick.
我不知道细节
I don't have the details.
那不是我的部门  你跟人力说去
That's not my department. Take it up with HR.
简直是胡说八道
That's utter bullshit!
汉娜
Hannah.
你的耳朵肯定烫了
Your ears must've been burning.
-我们正在谈论你  -是吗
- We were just talking about you. - Were you?
对  芙兰问你是否真的请了病假
Yeah, Fran was asking if you've really been signed off sick.
抱歉  汉娜  我没有暗示什么
I'm sorry, Hannah. I didn't mean to imply anything.
-我们知道这对你打击很大  -对我们都是
- We know how hard it's hit you. - It has all of us.
我们没有了解调查的所有内容
We're not being properly looped in on the investigation.
我很抱歉如果你感觉
I'm sorry if you feel
我让你们失望了
I've let you all down.
没人有这个意思
No-one is suggesting that.
只是感觉一半的队伍都不见了
It just feels like half the team is missing.
在我们最需要人手的时候
When we can least afford it.
而且我们重重受阻
And we're being obstructed.
太可笑了  没人在阻碍你们
That is ridiculous. No-one is obstructing you!
那为什么花了一周我们才拿到肖恩的笔记本
So why has it taken nearly a week to get hold of Sean's laptop?
为什么我们从其他渠道找到了斯特凡·瓦盖奇
And why do we only find out second hand about Stefan Vargic
而他和肖恩的谋杀案明明存在着明显联系
when there's clearly a link between his and Sean's murders?
你能证明吗
Can you prove that?
两起谋杀使用的是同一种子弹
The same ammunition was used in both killings.
手工制作
It's handmade.
很特别
It's distinctive.
所以呢  有人做了一批子弹并卖给
So? Somebody makes a batch and flogs it
布里斯托的懒蛋混混
to all the ne'er-do-wells in Bristol.
这证明不了什么
It doesn't prove anything.
这证明两起案件有联系
It suggests there's a connection.
如果有联系我肯定会知道
Pretty sure I'd know about it if there was one.
你不能一周多不来
You can't just turn up after more than a week
然后突然出现用权力压我们
and start throwing your weight around, Billy.
我没有
I'm not.
那你为什么认为你知道任何有价值的信息呢
So, what makes you think you know anything remotely useful?
斯特凡·瓦盖奇是我的线人
Stefan Vargic was on my list.
什么
What?
他是我的线人
He was one of my contacts.
你为什么不告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us?
我现在告诉你们了
I'm telling you now.
那你怎么确定这两者之间没有联系
And what makes you so sure there's no connection?
瓦盖奇和他的人都是小混混  我就是知道
Vargic and his crew are total no-marks. I just know it.
他跟谁一起混
Who was he with?
克罗地亚家族  经营城里的一家餐厅
Croatian family, runs a restaurant in town.
只是小打小闹
They're small fry.
-但有人认为应该杀了他  -对
- Yet someone thought it worthwhile killing him? - Aye.
真是令人意外
That was a bit of a shocker.
我需要知道发生了什么
I need to know what's going on.
你个自私的无赖  比利
You're a selfish twat, Billy.
我很抱歉你这么想
I'm sorry you think that.
肖恩·哈达克被谋杀了
Sean Hardacre has been killed.
所以跟大家合作吧
So start being a team player.
我会分享我这边的线索  我保证
I'll share whatever I find out, I promise.
只是
Just...
只是再给我一两天
Just give me a day or two.
切换SIM卡
紧急情况  你需要什么服务
Emergency. Which service do you require?
请接警察
Police, please.
我有关于警察遇害事件的消息
I have information relating to the murder of the police officer.
我不想说
I'd rather not say.
不  抱歉  不行
No, I'm sorry, I can't.
我知道凶器在哪
Well, I know where the weapon is
用来杀他的凶器
which was used to kill him.
这招很妙
That was a smart play.
至少给我们争取了时间
Buys us a wee bit of time at least.
还有米密查家族收到的任何信息
And any information gets fed back to the Mimicas.
如果内鬼在屋里
If the source is in the room.
听着  我刚才的话不是真心的
Listen, I, I didn't mean what I said.
说我是个自私的无赖吗
About me being a selfish twat?
我认罪  法官大人
Guilty as charged, your honour.
听着  我知道
Look I-I know that...
我知道你在照顾他
..I know you're looking out for him.
你开玩笑吧  "没有证据"
You're joking, aren't you? "No evidence."
-他们是这么说的吗  -对  什么也没有  天呐
- Is that what they said? - Yeah, nothing. Jesus.
正是我要找的女人
Just the woman I'm looking for.
有人举报
Someone's called in a tip
杀死肖恩·哈达克的枪支
about the gun used to kill Sean Hardacre.
有印象吗
Ring any bells?
你想一起来吗
You fancy tagging along?
肯定
You bet.
有什么有趣的事吗
Anything interesting?
我们可能知道了一个谋杀凶器的下落
We may know the whereabouts of one of the murder weapons.
好
Ok.
随时通知我
Keep me informed.
卡巴夏先生
Mr Kabashi...
我们在你的车库里找到了这个
..we found it in your garage.
我的当事人对手枪一无所知
My client has no knowledge of the weapon
也不知为何在那
or how it got there.
所以有人栽赃了你吗
So, somebody planted it?
他是这么说的
That's what he says.
他愿意跟我们说说吗
Does he care to enlighten us?
你要离开多久
How long will you be gone?
也许两晚
Maybe two nights.
最多三晚
Three at most.
你知道自己要去干什么吗
And do you know what you're getting yourself into?
达沃跟我说了一点
Davor's told me a bit about it.
你能告诉我吗
Can you tell me?
你应该问他
You should ask him.
他一直称之为"克拉伊纳"
He always refers to it as "Krajina".
别走
Don't go.
我必须走
I have to.
克里斯申  拜托
Christian, please.
碧昂卡  别  你就...
Bianca, don't, just...
这是什么
What's this?
假的
It's fake.
我也给你做了一本  我们可以消失
I can get one made for you too, we could disappear,
以免无法挽回
before it's too late.
我不是你想象中的人
I'm not who you think I am.
我不会放弃你  克里斯申
I won't give up on you, Christian.
你有吗
我没睡
你有什么好担心的
我总是在想斯特凡
他把我们出卖给了警察吗
杂种
达沃想把我赶走吗
为什么
因为  你懂的
能扣下扳机
..you know, being able to pull the trigger?
克里斯申开枪打死了他  这对你没影响
达沃只是开心那混蛋死了
Davor is just glad the bastard's dead.
真的
Really.
听我说  我知道之前在哪看到过那辆车了
Listen to me, I know now wh-where I've seen that car before.
对对  我可以证明  只需给我...
Yes, yes! I can prove it! Just give me my...!
比利
Billy?
Billy.
他们就要靠岸了
They're about to dock.
那是哪里
Where is that?
安特卫普附近
Somewhere near Antwerp.
欢迎
Welcome.
你想看看吗
You want to look?
卡拉什尼科夫冲锋枪
Kalashnikov, hm?
不好吗
No?
或许你更喜欢手枪  对吗
Maybe you prefer a handgun instead, hey?
瓦尔特PPK手枪
Walther PPK.
希特勒就有一把
Hitler owned one.
猫王也是
So did Elvis.
砰
Bang!
我们说正事吧
Shall we get down to business?
好  我们说正事
Yeah, let's get to business.
给  别担心  这把坏了
Here, don't worry, it's broken.
看看吧
Have a look.
你来吗
You coming?
一切都是谎言
Everything's a lie!
Everything's a lie.
你说过  "我会告诉你
You said, "I'll tell you...
"如果有你需要知道的事"
"..if there's something you need to know."
克拉伊纳的答案就在这里
The answer to Krajina is here.
LAX项目  北约鲑鱼号潜艇
这是个很罕见的鸟
Quite a rare bird, this one,
或者我该说鱼
or, should I say fish.
这是洛索斯微型潜艇
It's a Losos Class midget submarine,
在俄语中是"鲑鱼"的意思  如果你们想知道
translates as "salmon" in Russian, you may like to know.
俄语
Russian?
苏联在冷战时期很擅长建造这种
They're rather used to specialise in this type of vessel
小型潜艇
during the Cold War.
用途多为支持破坏任务
Designed to support sabotage missions, that sort of thing.
它的排水量是多少
And how much can she carry?
大概半吨吧
Up to half a metric ton, I'd say.
足够引起领地战争了
Enough to start a turf war.
天呐
Oh, my God.
他们打算用这个
And that's what they're gonna use
把毒品运进这个国家
to get the drugs into the country.
你要在哪停靠这种潜艇
And where would you dock a sub like this?
它可以在很浅的水域行进
She can operate in very shallow water.
我想大概需要用小船
I imagine you'd probably use a small boat
把货物送到岸上
to bring her cargo ashore.
所以可以停在任何地方
So, anywhere, basically.
它可以行驶几百海里
She has a range of several hundred nautical miles,
从它的母舰上
from her mother ship.
-母舰  -对
- Mother ship? - Yes.
有趣的是
And funnily enough,
安特卫普周围正好有一艘符合要求的舰艇
there's one that fits the bill operating out of Antwerp right now.
亚历山大·涅夫斯基号
The Alexander Nevsky,
苏联海军于90年代中期将其退役
decommissioned by the Russian Navy in the mid 90's,
也许是在同一时期
probably about the same time
狡猾的小鲑鱼也赋闲在家了
that our slippery little salmon was put out to pasture.
它被改造为货运用船
She's been refitted as a merchant vessel.
没错
Exactly.
只要母舰离港  你就知道
You'll know when they're going to launch our sub
他们要发射潜艇了
once she leaves the harbour.
就是这个
This is it.
这就是克拉伊纳
This is Krajina.